Guide to the Geoffrey T. Hellman Papers MSS.050
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 4: Casuals
  - E, F, 1940-1963; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - G, H, 1936-1968; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - I, J, K, 1940-1963; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - M, 1895-1956; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - N, O, R, 1950-1963; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - T, U, V, 1939-1963; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - W, 1938-1963; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Untitled, undated; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Series 5: Onward and Upward
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Elizabethan Club, 1942-1959; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Hearst's Art Collection, 1941; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Post, Emily, 1948-1955; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Final Version, 1963; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Research, 1914-1962; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Notes, undated; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Early Drafts, undated; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Final Draft, undated; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Original Manuscript, 1958; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: Rich Writers Correspondence, Reviews, and Finances, 1957-1963; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts: The Stuart Collection, 1941-1947; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts And Sciences: American Philosophical Society, 1959; 31142040616107 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Onward And Upward With The Sciences: Peabody Museum Drafts and Final, 1961-1962; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Onward And Upward With The Sciences: Peabody Museum Publications, 1869-1961; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Onward And Upward With The Sciences: Peabody Museum Research and Correspondence, 1832-1964; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Onward and Upward With The Sciences: Peabody Museum Correspondence About Museum History Project, 1963-1965; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Onward And Upward With The Social Sciences: Cyclopedia of Commercial and Business Anecdotes, 1947-1948; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Series 6: A Reporter at Large
  - 1 A-W, 1932-1960; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Hall of Fame, 1926-1962; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sachs, Alexander, 1944-1955; 31142040616131 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Series 7: World War II
  - Office of Inter-American Affairs, 1942-1944 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Office of Strategic Services, 1944-1955 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Post-War Correspondence Regarding Military, 1945-1955 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Profiles B-G, 1942-1964 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Profiles H-M, 1943-1948 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Casuals, 1943-1952 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - That Was The War, 1944-1950 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Other Publications, 1942-1946 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Series 8: Other Articles in The New Yorker
  - The Department of Amplification, 1955-1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - That Was New York, 1934-1941 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - That Was New York: Central Park Obelisk, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Series 9: The New Yorker Style
  - Editorial Personnel List, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Policy And Purpose Booklet, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Lampoon Parody, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - In-house Newsletter, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Participation Trust And Plan Bulletin, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Reprints of articles by The New Yorker staff, 1946-1947 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Series 10: Other Publications
  - P, V, 1941; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Advertising Copy, 1938-1939; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - American Heritage, 1862-1962; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Art in America John Canaday Profile, 1962-1964; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Art in America Museum of Modern Art, 1944-1959; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Art in America Museum of Modern Art Correspondence, 1963-1969; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Art in America Museum of Modern Art Drafts, Notes, and Sources, 1939-1963; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Author's Guild Bulletin, 1963; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Cosmopolitan, 1970-1971; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Fortune, 1933-1940; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Grolier Club, 1958-1964; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Holiday, 1961-1962; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Holiday, 1963; 31142040616156 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Life Style and Correspondence, 1936-1946; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Life Broun, Heywood, 1938; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Life Disney, Walt, 1940-1949; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Life Hitchcock, Alfred, 1939; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Life Luckman, Charles, 1946-1954; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Life McGuire, Dorothy, 1941; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Life Rinehart, Mary Roberts, 1946; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Life Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1940; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Life Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1941; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Life Saroyan, William, 1940; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Magazine of the Year, The, 1946-1947; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Menorah Journal, The, 1938; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Promenade 1941, 1947; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, 1947-1959; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Time, 1951-1952; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Venture, 1969; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - White Collar Zoo, 1949; 31142040616164 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Art in America. New York: McGraw Hill Book Company, Inc. Vol. 50, No. 3. Fall, 1962., 31142040616164 (Box 46A, Folder 31)
  - Art in America. New York: McGraw Hill Book Company, Inc. Vol. 52, No. 1. February, 1964., 31142040616164 (Box 46A, Folder 32)
  - Dodd Mead "Books for Fall 1947", 31142040616164 (Box 46A, Folder 33)
  - Holiday, v.32 no. 6; December, 1962, 31142040616164 (Box 46A, Folder 34)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, v. XXX; no. 39; 1947., 31142040616164 (Box 46A, Folder 35)
- Series 11: Books
  - How To Disappear For An Hour Undated Edited Galleys, 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour Reviews, 1947-1948; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour Business Contracts and Book Promotions, 1945-1953; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour Correspondence, 1941-1965; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour Undated Publicity Statement, 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour Correspondence about German version, 1962; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. De Peyster's Parties Undated Draft, 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Mrs. De Peyster's Parties Letter to Barrytown Explorer from Hellman, 1902-1969; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. De Peyster's Parties Typeset Table of Contents, 1968; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. De Peyster's Parties Book Jacket, 1963; 31142040616172 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Mrs. De Peyster's Parties Correspondence, 1962-1966; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Mrs. De Peyster's Parties Reviews, 1963-1964; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Hellman, Geoffrey. Clip File Vol. 1 1930-1941 (Album 56)
  - Hellman, Geoffrey. Clip File Vol. 2 1942-1953 (Album 57)
- Series 12: Unpublished Articles
  - Beebe, Lucius, 1941-1949; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Ewing, Dr. James Undated, 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library Undated Drafts, 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library Research and Correspondence, 1809-1964; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library Research Talk of the Town Tearsheets, 1935-1962; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library Publications, 1952-1964; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Rothko Chapel and Broken Obelisk Press Clippings, 1969-1971; 31142040616180 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Series 13: Correspondence
  - A, B, 1933-1961; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - C, 1933-1969; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - D-H, 1945-1966; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Gill, Brendan, 1946-1969; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph, 1940-1948; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - J-K, 1932-1969; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - L-O, 1932-1969; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - MacDonald, Dwight, 1945-1957; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - McKelway, St. Clair, 1936-1960; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - P-R, 1939-1969; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Ross, Harold Correspondence, 1934-1968; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Ross, Harold Articles About, 1948-1963; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Ross, Harold Editing Style, undated; 31142040616198 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - S, 1936-1969; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Shawn, William, 1935-1969; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - T-Z, 1926-1968; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Taylor, Robert, 1945-1967; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - White, E. B. and Katharine, 1936-1969; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - White, Katharine Editing Style, 1935; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - No Surname, 1941-1959; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Series 14: Speeches
  - C, L, R, 1954-1964; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Century Club, 1959-1968; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Coffee House, 1954; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Grolier Club, 1955-1962; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - New York Historical Society, 1963-1968; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - PEN International Association of Writers, 1968; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Princeton University, 1965; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - St. Paul's School, 1956-1957; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Series 15: Personal
  - Coleopterist's Society, 1969; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Grolier Club, 1952-1969; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Miss Fine's School Literary Contest, 1962; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - New York Historical Society Pintard Fellows, 1967-1969; 31142040616206 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Series 16: Finances
  - Agreements, 1941-1968; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, F-R Publishing Corp., 1935; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Breakage sheets, 1947-1969; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Credit account slips, 1946-1959; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Credit account slips, 1960-1969; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Drawing account balance sheets, 1952-1959; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Drawing account balance sheets, 1960-1969; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Surplus Paid sheets, 1947-1968; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers, 1940-1969; 31142040616214 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Oversize - Series 1: Talk of the Town
  - A Galleys, 1946-1964 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - B Galleys, 1945-1964 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - C Galleys, 1946-1964 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - D,E Galleys, 1945-1964 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - F Galleys, 1946-1963 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - G Galleys, 1945-1963 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - H-J Galleys, 1945-1963 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - K Galleys, 1948-1963 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - L Galleys, 1946-1963 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - M Galleys, 1945-1963 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - N Galleys, 1946-1969 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - O,P Galleys, 1945-1964 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Octogenarians Galleys, 1948-1958 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Party Roundups Galleys, 1950-1963 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Q, R Galleys, 1945-1967 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Rewrites Galleys, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - S Galleys, 1946-1964 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Style Galleys, 1953-1963 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - T Galleys, 1945-1963 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - U, V Galleys, 1947-1964 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - W Galleys, 1946-1964 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Y, Z Galleys, 1946-1963 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Anecdotes Galleys, 1946-1961 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Notes and Comments Galleys, 1945-1963 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Rewrites Editorial Proofs, 1945-1963 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Style Editorial Proofs, 1951-1963 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Anecdotes Editorial Proofs, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Notes and Comments Editorial Proofs, 1946-1963 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Editorial Proofs, undated (Box Map case, Folder 100)
  - Wodehouse, P. G., undated (Folder 5 Left)
  - "Talk of the Town" Page Proof, 1951 (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 7)
  - Notes and Comments Research Material Bell Telephone Company of New York, undated (Folder 10 Left)
- Oversize - Series 2: Profiles
  - Achelis, Elisabeth Research "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Arnold, Stanley Research "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Avinoff, Dr. Andrey Galleys, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - Biddle, George Galleys and "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1936-1961 (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - Borge, Victor Galleys and "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - Cerf, Bennett Galleys and Casual Galleys, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - Crane, Joe Galleys, undated (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - Dale, Chester Galleys, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - D'Harnoncourt, Rene Galleys, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Donon, Joseph Galleys, undated (Box 21, Folder 111)
  - Fairchild, Sherman Galleys, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Fish, Hamilton "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Hammer, Armand "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - Ketcham, Howard Galleys, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 115)
  - Knopf, Alfred Galleys and "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1947-1962 (Box 21, Folder 116)
  - Le Corbusier, Galleys and "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 117)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Research "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1947-1963 (Box 22, Folder 118)
  - Phillippe, Claudius Charles Galleys and Research Material, 1934-1954 (Box 22, Folder 119)
  - Restaurant Associates "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 120)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon Galleys, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 121)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon Research Material "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1949-1962 (Box 22, Folder 122)
  - Service, Robert Galleys, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 123)
  - Simon and Schuster "Talk of the Town" and Casual Galleys, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 124)
  - Sonnenberg, Ben Galleys and Research, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 125)
  - Turck, Fenton Galleys, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 126)
  - Whelan, Grover A. Galleys, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 127)
  - Achelis, Elisabeth Editorial Proofs, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 128)
  - Arnold, Stanly Editorial Proofs, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 129)
  - Biddle, George "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 130)
  - Cerf, Benett Research Material and Editorial Proofs, 1945-1959 (Box 23, Folder 131)
  - Countess Mara Inc. Editorial proofs, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 132)
  - Cullman, Howard "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 133)
  - Dale, Chester Editorial Proofs and Research Material, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 134)
  - Day, Joseph Research Material, 1930-1932 (Box 23, Folder 135)
  - D'Harnoncourt, Rene Editorial Proofs, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 136)
  - Donon, Joseph Editorial Proofs, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 137)
  - Fish, Hamilton "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1958-1968 (Box 23, Folder 138)
  - Gallatin, Albert Undated "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs (Box 23, Folder 139)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel Undated Research Material (Box 23, Folder 140)
  - Ketcham, Howard Editorial Proofs, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 141)
  - Knopf, Alfred Editorial Proofs, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 142)
  - Le Corbusier, Editorial Proofs, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 143)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Research, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 144)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Research "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1947-1965 (Box 23, Folder 145)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Research "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 146)
  - Restaurant Associates Editorial Proofs and Talk of the Town Editorial Proofs, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 147)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon Editorial Proofs, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 148)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 149)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Editorial proofs, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 150)
  - Service, Robert Undated Editorial proofs (Box 23, Folder 151)
  - Service, Robert Undated Research material (Box 23, Folder 152)
  - Service, Robert "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 153)
  - Sonnenberg, Ben Editorial Proofs, "Talk of the Town" Editorial Proofs, and Research Material, 1940-1959 (Box 23, Folder 154)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Editorial Proofs, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 155)
  - Whalen, Grover A. Editorial Proofs and Research Material Map Case Under H, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 156)
  - Donon, Joseph Undated Poster (Folder 9 Left)
  - Fairchild, Sherman Undated Page Proofs (Folder 8 Left)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Research Material, 1971 (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 4)
  - Powers, Bertram A. Research, 1963 (Folder 6 Left)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Research Material, undated (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 1)
- Oversize - Series 3: Subject Category
  - Calder, Alexander, Talk of the Town Galleys, 1948-1961 (Box 38, Folder 147)
  - Calder, Alexander Onward and Upward with the Arts Galleys, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 148)
  - Cooper Union Research "Talk of the Town" Galleys, 1946-1962 (Box 38, Folder 149)
  - Crowninshield, Frank Profile Galleys, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 150)
  - Crowninshield, Frank - That Was New York Galleys, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 151)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Casuals Galleys, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 152)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Casuals "Sorting Out The Seligmans" Varitype, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 153)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Talk of the Town Galleys, 1948-1963 (Box 38, Folder 154)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth Onward and Upward with the Arts Galleys, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 155)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth Profiles Galleys, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 156)
  - Museum of Natural History Research "Can We Save America" by Henry Osborn, undated (Box 38, Folder 157)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town A-L Galleys, 1949-1964 (Box 38, Folder 158)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town M-Z Galleys, 1951-1964 (Box 38, Folder 159)
  - Museum of Natural History A Reporter At Large Galleys, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 160)
  - Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers, Bones and Beetles Legal Documents, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 161)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Talk of the Town Galleys, 1948-1962 (Box 38, Folder 162)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Profiles Robbins, William J. Galleys, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 163)
  - Smithsonian Institution Talk of the Town Galleys, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 164)
  - Calder, Alexander Onward and Upward with the Arts Editorial Proofs, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 165)
  - Cooper Union Talk of the Town Editorial Proofs, 1946-1968 (Box 39, Folder 166)
  - Crowninshield, Frank Profile Research Material, 1937-1942 (Box 39, Folder 167)
  - Crowninshield, Frank That Was New York Editorial Proofs, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 168)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Schiff-Warburg Research Warburg Genealogical Chart, undated (Box 39, Folder 169)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Schiff-Warburg Research Warburg Genealogical Chart, undated (Box 39, Folder 170)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Editorial Proofs, 1951-1963 (Box 39, Folder 171)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth Onward and Upward with the Arts Editorial Proofs, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 172)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town A-D Editorial Proofs, 1947-1968 (Box 39, Folder 173)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town E-G Editorial Proofs, 1947-1964 (Box 39, Folder 174)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town H-L Editorial Proofs, 1951-1969 (Box 39, Folder 175)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town P-Z Editorial Proofs, 1948-1966 (Box 39, Folder 176)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town Page Proof, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 177)
  - Museum of Natural History A Reporter At Large Editorial Proofs, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 178)
  - Museum of Natural History Profile The American Museum I Editorial Proofs, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 179)
  - Museum of Natural History Profile The American Museum Editorial Proofs, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 180)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Talk of the Town Editorial Proofs, 1946-1967 (Box 39, Folder 181)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Profiles Robbins, William Editorial Proof, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 182)
  - Smithsonian Institution Research Material, 1965-1969 (Box 39, Folder 183)
  - Smithsonian Institution Talk of the Town Editorial Proofs, 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 184)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile The Enigmatic Bequest Editorial Proofs, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 185)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile The Enigmatic Bequest II Editorial Proofs, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 186)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile The Enigmatic Bequest Editorial Proofs, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 187)
  - Smithsonian Institution Undated Octopus on the Mall Book Advertisement (Box 39, Folder 188)
  - American Museum of Natural History Frank M. Chapman's Scrapbook (on shelf), 1933-1934 (Box 39, Folder 189)
  - Smithsonian Institution Bohn's Hand-book of Washington by C. Bohn (on shelf)., 1857 (Box 39, Folder 190)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Research "Our Crowd" Genealogical Chart, undated (Folder 18 Right)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town Research for "Venezuela of the Bronx" Galley File, 1969 (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 3)
  - Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town Research Museum Bicentennial Poster, 1956 (Folder 14 Right)
  - Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers, Bones, and Beetles Page Proofs, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 194)
  - Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers, Bones, and Beetles Foundry Proof, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 195)
  - Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers, Bones, and Beetles Final Galley, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 196)
  - The New Yorker at N.Y.U. Poster, 1983 (Folder 16 Right)
- Oversize - Series 4: Casuals
  - Galleys A-H, 1941-1960 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Galleys I-W, 1940-1963 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Editorial Proofs, 1953-1963 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Oversize - Series 5: Onward and Upward
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts Galleys Rich Writers, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts Talk of the Town Galleys, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts New York Times Magazine Regarding Rich Writers Tearsheets, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts The Stuart Collection Galleys, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts And Sciences: Galleys American Philosophical Society, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 23)